Some friends come with a happy ending.
Friends with Benefits is a romance, comedy film directed by Will Gluck.
Dylan is done with relationships.
Jamie decides to stop buying into the Hollywood clichés of true love.
When the two become friends they decide to try something new and take advantage of
their mutual attraction - but without any emotional attachment.
Dylan Harper, played by Justin Timberlake.
Jamie Rellis, played by Mila Kunis.
Annie Harper, played by Jenna Elfman.
Lorna, played by Patricia Clarkson.
Tommy Bollinger, played by Woody Harrelson.
Mr. Harper, played by Richard Jenkins.
Friends with Benefits is a 2011 American romantic comedy film directed by
Will Gluck and starring Justin Timberlake and Mila Kunis.
The film features Patricia Clarkson, Jenna Elfman, Bryan Greenberg, Nolan
Gould, Richard Jenkins, and Woody Harrelson in supporting roles.
The plot revolves around Dylan Harper (Timberlake) and Jamie Rellis (Kunis), who meet in New York
City, and naively believe adding sex to their friendship will not lead to complications.
Over time, they begin to develop deep feelings for each other,
only to deny it each time they are together.
Principal casting for Friends with Benefits took place over a
three-month period from April to July 2010.
Gluck reworked the original script and plot shortly
after casting Timberlake and Kunis.
Filming began in New York City on July 20, 2010, and
concluded in Los Angeles in September 2010.
Screen Gems distributed the film, which was released
in North America on July 22, 2011.
Friends with Benefits received positive reviews from critics upon release,
most of whom praised the chemistry between the lead actors.
The film emerged as a commercial success at the box office, grossing
$149.5 million worldwide, against a budget of $35 million.
It was nominated for two People's Choice Awards—Favorite Comedy Movie, and Favorite Comedic
Movie Actress (Kunis)—and two Teen Choice Awards for Timberlake and Kunis.
The film explores themes of new york city, friendship, job
interview, dementia, alzheimer's disease.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.